Mine.
When I was with him,
you were who knows where.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
Where are your morals?
Where's your bottom line?
Where's your WeChat?
You wouldn't show your abs at your concert,
but you're flashing them like crazy here!
How could you
let the love you caught slip through your fingers?
Getting all fired up.
Isn't that a bit overboard?
I just called you a despicable villain,
now you're his despicable villain.
I'm his past!
And he's my dark past!
I'm HR.
Office romances aren't allowed here.
Did you clear it with me?
I'm firing your little bunny right now.
If we keep hugging like this,
we're going to catch feelings.
Really.
I lost myself for a second.
Mom!
I don't know who that person is either.
Everyone has heard the story of Cinderella, right?
Whoever can fit into this,
will be my guy.
Kid,
hurry up and call us Dad One, Dad Two, and Dad Three.
Coming to this cafe every day,
I feel so happy.
Who forced me into such a state?
I'll point right in his face and say "You, sir!"
Oh no.
Come on!
The new loading zone, right?
All of you, stop it!
Trying to catch me?
I'm too slippery for that.
If you're being threatened, sister,
just blink.
I'm doing this voluntarily.
Since when did you become a detective?
What family curse?
I don't believe in Wuji at all.
You have no right to question me.
Secondly,
you're a suspect.
Don't give me that rich boy attitude.
I'm not a princess right now.
If I were a detective,
hand over your phones, one by one.
Give me the phone.
Bring one over.
Trying to hide key evidence?
Pop the balloons one by one.
The key evidence must be in the balloon fragments.
Is He Jiahuan so clever that he made up a story
that you happen to know but I don't?
So that's why I wanted to say this first.
Only Ayin, as a peer,
couldn't mess with me.
I just knocked him out.
And left him there.
To me,
the person who made the fake AI video didn't kill my ex-boyfriend.
He impersonated my dead ex-boyfriend to scam me out of my money.
You have to understand my previous motive.
But it was just my money that went missing.
Why would I be ready to kill at any moment?
No, no, no.
The killer wouldn't want to kill you.
It was just a last resort.
It's possible that right then, he had to take you out too.
This handwriting...
This stroke has a sharp hook.
This handwriting is the same as the writing on Cui Haowan.
How long have you worn glasses?
Aren't these all just memories from today?
Actually, their treatment trilogy is meant to make people sick.
Trilogy.
You escaped with a unanimous vote.
My...
Mine!